[
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CSE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ECE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "ME", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "IT", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "EE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "AI", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "DS", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "9.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "8.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.5", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["datascience"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["cybersecurity"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["webdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["python"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["java"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["C"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "beginner"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "intermediate"},
{"Question": "", "Answers": "", "Branch": "CE", "CGPA": "7.0", "Interested Fields": ["appdevelopment"], "Programming Language": ["Html/Css"], "Knowledge Level": "advanced"}

]

